Guide to the Kermit Carlyle Parsons papers, circa 1945-1999
Parsons, Kermit Carlyle papers, circa 1945-1999
- Series II. Nathaniel Owings Archive Project
  - Other Projects
    - Other Publications
      - A Proposal from the Citizens of Tioga-Nicetown, Inc for an Agreement with the Temple University Health Sciences Center Prepared by SOM, June 1970 (Box 40)
- Series III. Research and Consulting
  - "The University in Urban Change", Georgia Davis, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - "The University on Urban Change": drafts, notes, correspondence, ca. 1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - "The University in Urban Change": presentation, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    correspondence, thesis outline, notes, articles, memos, Georgia K. Davis biographical data
  - "The University in Urban Change": correspondence, 1968 - 1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "The University in Urban Change": drafts, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - "The University in Urban Change": draft, draft outline, notes, map, "The Community and the Expansion of Columbia University" report, ca. 1967 - 1970 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - "The University in Urban Change", ca. 1971 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - "The University in Urban Change", 1971 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - University District renewal, 1965 - 1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Urban renewal and universities - papers, articles, brochures, 1948 - 1970 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - "Urban Renewal in American Universities", 1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Community Renewal Program Report, City of Providence, Rhode Island, 1965 - 1970 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Urban Planning and Redevelopment, Philadelphia,Pennsylvania - papers, articles, brochures, 1960 - 1970 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Urban Planning and Development: Parking - guide, reports and article, 1950 - 1970 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Urban Planning and Development: Bay D-Espoir, Newfoundland, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - "Campus/Community Relationships: An annotated bibliography", 1971 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - "When is the Twentieth Century?", ALA Dinner, R.W. Morse, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - "The Terms of the Truce Between Universities and Cities": draft, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - "The Terms of the Truce Between Universities and Cities": Notes and correspondence, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - "Seven Unknowns in Planned City Building": Correspondence, 1968 - 1969 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - "An Annotated Bibliography on University Planning and Development": Correspondence, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Woodlawn's Model Cities Plan: A Demonstration of Citizen Responsibility, preliminary draft, pages 1-87, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Woodlawn's Model Cities Plan: A Demonstration of Citizen Responsibility, preliminary draft, pages III-1 - V-121, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Woodlawn's Model Cities Plan: A Demonstration of Citizen Responsibility, preliminary draft, pages V1-1 - VI-63, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Woodlawn's Model Cities Plan: A Demonstration of Citizen Responsibility, preliminary draft, pages AP-1 - AP-135, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - "The Urban University and its Role in Urban Design", 1967 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Background Data and Analysis Phase of the Utica Downtown Planning Study, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Summary Report: Utica Downtown Planning Study, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Amendment Number Two to the Plant Program for St. Petersburg Junior College, 1965 - 1971 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - University of California New Campus Location Criteria report, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Hatch-White, Architects, "Campus Guide Lines" correspondence, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - State Information Data Sheet, higher education, 1956 - 1964 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - "Urban Design and Planning -- The Swedish Experience": correspondence, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Zoning, Broome County and Ithaca, NY(Tompkins County), ca. 1950 - 1960 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Classrooms for How Many? enrollment handbook, State of New York Commission on School Buildings, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Estimates of Future School Employment, School District #6, Elmira - Big Flats, ca. 1953 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Notebook on State University of New York (SUNY) Planning, part 1, ca. 1963 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Notebook on State University of New York (SUNY) Planning, part 2, ca. 1963 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Notebook on State University of New York (SUNY) Planning, part 3, ca. 1963 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Notebook on State University of New York (SUNY) Planning, part 4, ca. 1963 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Concrete: Design and Construction, draft, State University Construction Fund, Albany, NY, May 3, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - "Application of Performance in a Major Building Program", speech, October 26, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    speech given at The Building Research Advisory Board Symposium, Chicago, IL, about program of the State University of New York(SUNY)
  - Action Program Reports, State University of New York (SUNY) Schools: Alfred, Cobleskill, Stony Brook, Albany, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Action Program Reports, State University of New York (SUNY) Schools: Brockport, Potsdam, Delhi, Oneonta, 1965- 1966 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1963 - 1968 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    correspondence, proposal
  - "Planning a New City: Irvine, California", n.d. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "Population Goals for Orange County: A Search for Meaningful Policy", Raymond L. Watson, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - City Planning: Newsclippings, articles, pamphlets, 1937 - 1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Town and Country Planning Act 10 & 11 Geo. 6 Ch. 51, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Town and Country Planning (Amendment) Act 14 & 15 Geo. 6 Ch. 19, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Town and Country Planning Act 1 & 2 Eliz. 2 Ch. 16, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - New Towns: Specific communities, 1951 - 1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - The British New Towns Policy, 1953 - 1956 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - John W. Reps, planning, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - John W. Reps, publications, ca. 1967 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, forms, clippings, ca. 1965 - 1972 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Bibliographies, ca. 1968 - 1971 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Conferences and institutes, 1970 - 1971 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - American Institute of Architects membership certificate, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - "Planning and Urban Land Policy", John W. Reps, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Planning and development, Chicago, Illinois, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Land use and development in the Netherlands, ca. 1965 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Statistical data, ca. 1967 - 1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, teaching assistantships, 1970 - 1971 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD) publications, 1970 - 1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Mailing lists, ca. 1970 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Outline of New Towns planning seminar and research, ARCH 502, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Planning and development, various communities, 1970 - 1972 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - AG conference mailing list, July 8, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - City planning, Irvine, California, ca. 1971 - 1972 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Center for Yrban Development research proposals, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - "Legal Authority in an Extralegal Setting: The Case of Land Rights in Jakarta, Indonesia" by Leaf, November 1, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - "Rochester Gateway Study" Draft - Peer Review by Parsons, December 13, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - "New York's East river Drive: A Study of Infrastructure Planning and the Cycles of Urban Prosperity" by Gutfreund, November 9,1991 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - "Integrative Planning for the 'Joint Systems of Society and Technology - the Emerging Role of the University" by Jantsch, 1968-1969 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - "Abstracts" Office of Housing and Urban Programs, July 1990 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Ebenezer Howard and the Garden City, Spring 1998 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - The Commons - Ithaca, New York, 1970s (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - "Documenting the Planners", Documentation Newsletter, Fall 1985 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - National Growth Policy Articles, 1973-1974 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - A Proposal to the RPA for a Grant to Support a Study of Metropolitan Planning Policy Evaluation: The Regional Planning of New York and Its Environs, April 1970 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - A New American University, Steven Muller, January 1977 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Frederick Law Olmsted: A Register of His Papers in the Library of Congress, 1963 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Chapter 7 Notes - UDC Research Report, June 1972 (Box 70, Folder 13a)
  - Chapter 7 Notes - UDC Research Report, June 1972 (Box 70, Folder 13b)
  - Cornell University: Historic Building Survey of the Lower Campus, December 1978 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Ithaca, New York Downtown Plan, Preliminary Analysis. Prepared by Rogers Taliaferro & Lamb, February 1961 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Public Land Acquisition for the New Communities and the Control of Urban Growth: Alternative Strategies; Prepared by Parsons, Budke, Clemhout, Farrell, Prost, Roberts (Draft), February 1974 (Box 70, Folder 16a)
  - Public Land Acquisition for the New Communities and the Control of Urban Growth: Alternative Strategies; Prepared by Parsons, Budke, Clemhout, Farrell, Prost, Roberts (Draft), February 1974 (Box 70, Folder 16b)
  - Public Land Acquisition for the New Communities and the Control of Urban Growth: Alternative Strategies; Prepared by Parsons, Budke, Clemhout, Farrell, Prost, Roberts (Final), February 1974 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - National Growth Policy: An Institutional Perspective, November 1976 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Campus Correspondence, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Cornell History, 1980s (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - A Conceptual Framework fro Study and Action to Reform Architectural Education: A Study Proposal; Deans of the Consortium of Eastern Schools of Architecture, January 1974 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Land Reports (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Land Acquisition Project Notes, 1971-1972 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Smithsonian Institute Files, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous Real Estate Reports, Land Acquisition Notes, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 25a)
  - Miscellaneous Real Estate Reports, Land Acquisition Notes, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 25b)
  - UDC Interview Notes (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Book digests (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Ithaca Planning Reports, 1961-1963 (Box 70, Folder 28a)
  - Ithaca Planning Reports, 1961-1963 (Box 70, Folder 28b)
  - Campus Planning at the University of Puerto Rico, Correspondence, Notes, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 29a)
  - Campus Planning at the University of Puerto Rico, Correspondence, Notes, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 29b)
  - Bibliography - History of City Planning; prepared by Thomas W. Mackesey, September 1959 (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - "A Student's Guide to Planning Literature" prepared by Etta Arntzen, 1956 (Box 70, Folder 31)
  - Parsons Interview Tapes - Carl Feiss, 1954 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Garden Cities Files, 1903 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Residential Design Guidelines, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Old Archive Correspondence and Notes, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Campus Planning Summaries, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Ithaca Urban Area Report, 1949 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Baltimore Downtown Strategy, Summer 1994 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - University Housing Reports, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - University City Concept Reports, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Campus Planning - Other Universities, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Ithaca Planning Reports, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Prospectus: Regional Planning Model of Nova Scotia Economy, Aug. 1967 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Canadian Planning Files, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 13a)
  - Canadian Planning Files, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 13b)
  - Testimony of Floyd B. McKissick to the Subcommittee on Housing and Community Development, September 29, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - State University Construction Fund Correspondence, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Campus Planning Correspondence, Notes, 1964-1965 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - An Annotated Bibliography on University and Medical Center Planning and Development, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Report - University Planning, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Schools and Recreation Notes, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Memoirs of Harold C. Bernhard, November 1979 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Metropolitan Boston Planning Files, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Housing Reports, 1952 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Milton Keynes Zone Educative Learning Area, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Milton Keynes Files, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Articles, 1974-1976 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Housing Articles, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - AID Report, September 1983 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - The 1960-1965 Capital Improvement Program recommended for the City of Ithaca, prepared by the Ithaca Planning Board, November 4, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - "The Crisis in Transportation" Draft, March 4, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Endowment for the Arts Reports (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Housing and Urban Renewal Articles, 1962-1967 (Box 71, Folder 31)
  - Capital Improvement Programming for Ithaca; prepared by the Ithaca Planning Board, November 26, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 32)
  - A Site Study for a Civic Center for Ithaca, prepared by the Ithaca Planning Board, Spring 1957 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Baltimore Inner Harbor Articles, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Tysons Corner Urban Center Study, September 4, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - President's Housing Committees, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - A Guide to Planning Literature, 2nd Addition, prepared by Etta Arntzen, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Historic Preservation in Tompkins County, December 1977 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Ithaca, NY: A General Plan, prepared by the City Planning Board, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Campus Planning Correspondence, 1961, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Campus Planning Correspondence, 1962-1965, 1962-1965 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Campus Planning Research Proposals, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - "One Way to Run a National Growth Policy (Second Draft)", prepared by KC Parsons, Pierre Clavel, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - "One Way to Run a National Growth Policy (Fourth Draft)", prepared by KC Parsons, Pierre Clavel, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Proposal on Development Guidance Projects, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - City Planning and Urban Renewal in Auburn, NY, prepared by KC Parsons, January 1960 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal Notes, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Ford Foundation Files - Urban Renewal Research, May 1969 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Parsons Ford Foundation Correspondence, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Canadian Land Banks, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - The Terms of Truce between Universities and Cities, Undated (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Long Range Needs and Opportunities in New York State, Working Papers, Undated (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - An Annotated Bibliography on University and Medical Center Planning and Development, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Book Review: Campus: An American Planning Tradition, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Office of Policy Development and Research Discussion Draft #1: Outline for Urban Policy Report, September 2, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Operational Advance Files, 1960s (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Philadelphia Planning Reports, 1964-1969 (Box 72, Folder 25a)
  - Philadelphia Planning Reports, 1964-1969 (Box 72, Folder 25b)
  - Case Western Reserve University Planning Program Files, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - New York City Planning Articles, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - "Physical Aspects of Open Space" by McCue, January 6, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - "Universities and Cities" by Parsons, 1963 (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - "Progress Report of the Board of Regents on the Regents Statewide Plan for the Expansion and Development of Higher Education", December 18, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - The Pittsburgh Goals Study, January 1972 (Box 72, Folder 31)
  - Putting Cooperation to Work, April 1972 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - News Articles on Higher Education, 1973-1975 (Box 72, Folder 33a)
  - News Articles on Higher Education, 1973-1975 (Box 72, Folder 33b)
  - "Support Cost Education" Higher Education Cost Report, undated (Box 72, Folder 34)
  - University Circle Financial Requirements, Memo, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 35)
  - The Battle of the Bill, 1965? (Box 72, Folder 36)
  - University of California: New Campus Location Criteria, 1958 (Box 72, Folder 37)
  - A Study of College and University Enrollments and Enrollment Trends in New York State, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 38)
  - A Method for Estimating Physical Facilities for a New College, June 4, 1963 (Box 72, Folder 39)
  - Organization for Campus Planning, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 40)
  - European Universities, 1963 (Box 72, Folder 41)
  - Chapter II: The Form of the American College Campus, undated (Box 72, Folder 42)
  - The Report of the New York University Task Force on the Financial Emergency, May 19, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 43)
  - South East Chicago Renewal Project No. 1, January 1955? (Box 72, Folder 44)
  - "The West Philadelphia Corporation" Brochure, undated (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - University City, Philadelphia Map, prepared by the West Philadelphia Corporation, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - "Chapter 3 - Case Study, University City", undated (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - "Contrasting Concepts in Campus Planning", Prepared by the Society for College and University Planning, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - "The Changing Campus: People and Process", Prepared by the Society for College and University Planning, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - "Morningside Heights Core Area Study" Prepared by Morningside Heights, Inc., May 2, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Chicago Research - Notes, Articles, and Correspondence, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - College Impact Planning Articles - Abrams and Croberg, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Housing Articles, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Community Colleges & Urban Renewal, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Universities, Colleges Operate as Major Force in Local Renewal Programs, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report - University Hill Corporation, 1964-1965 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - A College in the City: An Alternative, 1960s (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Forged in Crisis: Washington, DC's three new colleges, September 1968 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Campus Planning - Questionnaire Responses, March 1, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - New York State United Ministries of Higher Education Long Range Planning, December 1970 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - 2-Year College Planning - New York, Dec 16, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Keuka College, December 1966 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Middlesex County Community College Study, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - One Way to Run a National Growth Policy, May 15, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Overview of Population Forecasting for Small Areas, June 1975 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Ithaca / Tompkins County: Economic Base, Schools Reports, 1956 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - 1961-1966 Capital Improvement Program- Ithaca, NY, 1960 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Greater Ithaca 1959 Annual Report, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Ithaca Renewal, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Mass Transportation - Ithaca, NY, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Planning for Today and Tomorrow, March 1959 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - 1962-1966 Capital Improvement Program- Ithaca, NY, December 1961 (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - "An Environmental Analysis of Streit with Reference to Damage and Theft", prepared by Jean Shorett, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Private Groups in Public Planning, 1949 (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Neghborhood Planning Programs, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - North Carolina's Plan for Urban Training and Research, January 1965 (Box 73, Folder 32)
  - Institutional Planning Research, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 33)
  - University Policy Research Proposals, 1965-1966 (Box 73, Folder 34)
  - Early Drafts of University Planning Reports, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 35)
  - Ithaca Town Board Proposal - Bostwick Road Industrial District, 1954 (Box 73, Folder 36)
  - Town of Ithaca Articles, 1955 (Box 73, Folder 37)
  - Ithaca Housing Notes, 1960 (Box 73, Folder 38)
  - Carl Butler Notes, Undated (Box 73, Folder 39)
  - Town of Ithaca Planning Articles and Notes, 1958-1959 (Box 73, Folder 40)
  - Town of Ithaca Retail Facilities, 1958 (Box 73, Folder 41)
  - Town of Ithaca Planning Board Regulations, 1958 (Box 73, Folder 42)
  - Proposed Land Use, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 43)
  - Ithaca Regional Planning Board Files - Economic Analysis, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 44)
  - Town of Ithaca Zoning Ordinance, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 45)
  - "The University in Urban Change: A Study of City-University Renewal" prepared by KC Parsons and Georgia Davis, December 1969 (Box 73, Folder 46)
  - "The University in Urban Change: A Study of City-University Renewal" prepared by KC Parsons and Georgia Davis - Notes, December 1969 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - "The University and its Urban Environment" by KC Parsons and Georgia Davis, July 1971 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - "The University and its Urban Environment" by KC Parsons and Georgia Davis, July 1971 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - "Land Use Analysis" Master Plan Reports - City of East Providence, RI. Prepared by the Dept. of Planning and Urban Development, April 9, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - "Sanborn Services for City and Regional Planning" - Sanborn Map Company (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Long Range Needs and Opportunities in New York State: A Series of Working Papers, prepared by Barclay Jones and Burnham Kelly, July 1962 (Box 74, Folder 6a)
  - Long Range Needs and Opportunities in New York State: A Series of Working Papers, prepared by Barclay Jones and Burnham Kelly, July 1962 (Box 74, Folder 6b)
  - Proposal - Developing a Housing Strategy to Meet the Needs for Low and Moderate Income Housing in New York State, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Research Proposals: Cornell and Its Community, November 7, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - "State University Building Program - Goals, Accomplishments and Challenge for the Future" speech by Anthony G. Adinolfi, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Book Manuscript: The University in Urban Change - Draft I, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Book Manuscript: The University in Urban Change - Draft IVA, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Book Manuscript: The University in Urban Change - Draft for Minerva, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Book Manuscript: The University in Urban Change - Chapter III, Third Draft, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Book Manuscript: The University in Urban Change - Chapter II, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Book Manuscript: The University in Urban Change - Notes and Correspondence, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Book Manuscript: The University in Urban Change - Chapter II, Second Draft, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Book Manuscript: The University in Urban Change - Introduction, Second Draft, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Report to the Ontario Council on Graduate Studies on a Proposed Doctoral Program in Planning at the University of Toronto, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Envrionment and Health, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Land Uses in the United States in the Year 2000, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Design from Knowledge: Taboos, Logic, and Information, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Teaching Urban Desgin as a Decision-Making Process, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - A Linear Land Use Model, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - "Guidelines for the Expansion of Universities into Urban Renewal Areas" Draft, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - "Excerpt from the Architectural Record, Volume XII, 1907", 1907 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - Parsons Book Reviews, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Twin Tier New York State Counties - Higher Education Study, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - Hotels and Urban Renewal (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - New York State - The Location of Facilities for Higher Education, 1961-1962 (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - Contract with New York State Urban Development Corporation, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - Untitled Manuscript on the New York State Urban Development Corporation, undated (Box 74, Folder 31)